(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T17:05:30.960966",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
僕たちは配信アプリ、ホロキャスで活動する配信者！
We're holoCaster, streamers who active in the streaming app!
突然画面に吸い込まれて、アプリと繋がる謎の世界、ホロキャス界に来ちゃった！
Suddenly, we were sucked into the screen and came to holoCast World!
そこでは、現実で苦しむ人の魂が怪物化してしまう現象、夢落ちが起きていた。
There, a phenomenon was happening where people suffering in reality turned into monsters.
怪物コラップサを倒して、みんなの魂を取り戻さないと！
We have to defeat the monster Kolapsa and get everyone's souls back!
そして、魔法少女に変身して戦うことになった。みんなの夢を助けて、夢を応援する！
And so, transforming into magical girls, we're going to fight! To save everyone's dreams and cheer them on!
それが、魔法少女ホロウィッチ！
That is... magical girl holoWitch!
今日はスペシャルハロウィンステージ！
Today is a special Halloween stage!
さらに、今をときめく超人気歌手のかなたさんも参加する、超々豪快イベント！
Even Kanata, the wildly popular singer, is participating. It's a super, super bold event!
で、その超豪快イベントのオープニングアクトをうちら6人が担当することになって。
And we, the six of us, get to do the opening act for that super bold event, so...
せっかくだし、みんなでホロウィッチの衣装を着て、ドカンと派手に盛り上げちゃおうかなって。
Since it's a special occasion, we're wearing holoWitch outfits to really liven things up and make a big splash!
でも、いいのかなあ？
Wait, is that okay?
魔法とか、妖精とか、一応内緒なんだけど。
Magic and fairies are supposed to be secret, right?
今日はハロウィンだから、仮装ってことにすれば、なんとかなるなら！
Well, it's Halloween, so if we say it's cosplay, maybe we can get away with it!
そうそう！って、そろそろ準備したほうがよくない？
Right, right! Then shouldn't we start getting ready soon?
そうだね！じゃあ、気合を入れていきますか！
That's right! Then let's put our all into it!
ホロウィッ、ク、トリーッ、ト……
holoWitch, trick or...
ト！
Treat!
ねっちゅ ねっちゅ ねっちゅ 足りないでしょ
Nechu, nechu, nechu, is it not enough?
こっちおいで 遊ぼうよ！
Come on over and let's play!
ねっちゅーシンドローム
Necchu Syndrome
いざはい いざはいして いざはい いざはいして
Go ahead and play! Go ahead and play!
楽しくいられないために全力
To happily enjoy yourself, give it your all!
イライラしてたら魂抜けるもったいない！
If you get irritated, you'll lose your soul. What a waste!
「どうしたら喜んでくれるかな」ばっか
What should we do to make you happy?
思いついては即行動 スマイルハンター
Thinking of it makes you act on it. Smile hunter!
こっそり君のツボ ピンポイント
Secretly targeting your sweet spot.
撃ち抜いちゃう 成功魔法だもん 愛の呪文
Nailing it with magic, our spell of love!
フルキャスト コンサート まだまだ仕掛けちゃえ！
Full cast concert! We're still just getting started!
あっという間に つかまえた
In a flash, we caught you!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー シンドローム いたずらからのハピネス
Nechu, nechu, nechu syndrome! Mischief happiness!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー したらキュン 照れ隠しで スマイル ニッ
Nechu, nechu, nechu, making you grin. Smiling through shyness!
年中無休 カーニバル 好き重なれば
Year-round carnival, when loves pile up,
年中無休 カーニバル お祭り ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー 足りない！ こっちおいで 遊ぼうよ！
Year-round carnival, it's a festival! Nechu, nechu, nechu, is it not enough? Come on over and let's play!
とにかく楽しんじゃおう ほらね！
Anyway, let's have fun!
プランは完璧 アドレナリンはどばどば出しちゃうんです
Our plan is foolproof! Letting the adrenaline rush!
ここをこうしたら みんながびっくりしてさ～
If we do this here, everyone will be so surprised!
ちょっと待って 私の出番は？ つまりどういうこと？？
Wait a minute, when is my turn? What's going on here?!
もうめちゃめちゃだ～ 始まりは違っても 同じ道行く
It's a total mess! Even if we start differently, we walk the same path.
ピーキーだって 集まれば つまり最強じゃん？
We might be quirky, but if we gather, we're the strongest, right?
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー シンドローム 高鳴りすぎて 発熱
Nechu, nechu, nechu syndrome! Over-amplified fever!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー しとこ？ とっておきのウィンク はい！
Nechu, nechu, nechu, let's do this! Our favorite wink!
異世界から見せたい 両手いっぱいの愛 こんなにも近くにいるよ
All the love seen from another world, so close to us now.
年中無休で笑いたい 君と笑い合いたいのに
We want to smile all year round and laugh together with you.
やんやんちゃちゃしてたら いつの間にか救えちゃう
If we keep acting wild, before we know it, we save people.
幸せすぎて困っちゃう つかまえたら離さない
We're so happy it's troublesome! Once we get you, we won't let go!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー シンドローム いたずらからのハピネス
Nechu, nechu, nechu syndrome! Mischief happiness!
ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー したらキュン 照れ隠しで スマイル ニッ
Nechu, nechu, nechu, making you grin. Smiling through shyness!
年中無休 カーニバル 好き重なれば
Year-round carnival, when loves pile up,
年中無休 カーニバル お祭り ねっちゅー ねっちゅー ねっちゅー 足りない！ こっちおいで 遊ぼうよ！
Year-round carnival, it's a festival! Nechu, nechu, nechu, is it not enough? Come on over and let's play!
とにかく楽しんじゃおう ほらね！
Anyway, let's have fun!
トリック・オア・トリート！
Trick or treat!
みんな、盛り上がってるー？
Are you guys getting hyped?
ホロウィッチのオープニングアクト、どうだったー？
How was HoloWitch's opening act?
ここからもっと、もっと盛り上げてくから、みんなで一緒に楽しもうね！
We're going to turn the energy up even more from here, so let's all have fun together!
今日は我々ホロキャスの配信者だけじゃなく、あの超人気歌手、カノンさんがゲストで来てくださってます！
Today, not only us HoloCast streamers, but that super popular singer, Kanon-san, has come as our guest!
カノンさん、どうぞー！
Kanon-san, please!
トリック・オア・トリート。
Trick or treat.
みんな、今日は最後までよろしくね。
Everyone, let's make it a great show until the very end today.
いやまさかさ、あのカノンさんと同じステージに立てるなんて。
I mean, to think I'd be able to stand on the same stage as Kanon-san.
いや本当、憧れですよ。
Seriously, she's my absolute idol.
カノンさんの歌を聴くと、すっごくパワーもらえるんだよな。
Listening to Kanon-san sing gives me so much power.
そっそ、こんなに頂いちゃっていいんですかっ！ってくらいね。
Right? Like, "Is it really okay for us to receive this much?!"
うん、めっちゃ元気でるよね。
Yeah, it really energizes you.
え？
Huh?
ありがとう。なんでもないから。
Thank you. It's nothing.
次の曲は、みんなも一緒に歌ってほしいんだな。
For the next song, I'd love for everyone to sing along with us.
君たち！遠慮しないで声出してね、声ー！
You guys! Don't hold back, let your voices be heard!
キミの声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
さあ冒険を始めよう 遊びたい ぜったい
Let's start the adventure, I want to play, absolutely!
とうたいっ! たいっ! たいっ! あいわな
I want to! Want to! Want to! I want to!
joy と joy と joy と pop な ベイビー
Joy and joy and joy and pop baby
joy と joy と joy と happy な ピーポー
Joy and joy and joy and happy people
ぱぴぷぺぽ ばぶぅ ベイビー!
Papi pupe po babu baby!
joy と joy と joy と pop な ベイビー
Joy and joy and joy and pop baby
joy と joy と joy と happy な ピーポー
Joy and joy and joy and happy people
弱虫なんかじゃない 自信ありげにピースサイン
I'm not a wimp, with a confident peace sign
キミのその目にキスして 笑いたい ぜったい
Kissing your eyes, I want to laugh, absolutely
とうたいっ! たいっ! たいっ! あいわな
I want to! Want to! Want to! I want to!
joy と joy と joy と pop な ベイビー
Joy and joy and joy and pop baby
joy と joy と joy と happy な ピーポー
Joy and joy and joy and happy people
ぱぴぷぺぽ ばぶぅ ベイビー!
Papi pupe po babu baby!
joy と joy と joy と happy な セイエーーイ
Joy and joy and joy and happy say yeah!
キミの心はそうもっとドキドキ 僕の心もそうずきずきぞくぞく弾けてるんじゃない？
Isn't your heart beating faster, and my heart throbbing and thrilling?
いつじょいふる ふぉびふぅ で ぼぶぅ ばぶぅ
It's joyful fobifu de bobu babu
joy と joy と joy と pop な ベイビー
Joy and joy and joy and pop baby
joy と joy と joy と happy な ピーポー
Joy and joy and joy and happy people
ドキドキしちゃうのなんでだろ？ ゾクゾクしちゃうのなんでだろ？
Why is my heart pounding? Why is it thrilling?
この指にとまるのはどんな運命なんだろ？
What kind of fate rests upon this finger?
ぜんぶしたいな じょいふるだけじゃ終っちゃう
I want to do it all, just joyful would end it
エブリバディ いつもわそう、いついつもこの時も
Everybody always, always, even at this time
最終系はきっと修正なしで！
The final version without a doubt, unedited!
どうせ we do we do we do do
Do we do we do we do do
ぱぴぷぺぽ ぱぴぷぺぽ 痛いっ！とうたいっ！
Papi pupe po papi pupe po, it hurts! I want to!
joy と joy と joy と pop な ベイビー
Joy and joy and joy and pop baby
joy と joy と joy と happy な ピーポー
Joy and joy and joy and happy people
joy と joy と joy と happy な セイエーーイ
Joy and joy and joy and happy say yeah!
キミの心はそうもっとドキドキ 僕の心もそうずきずきぞくぞく弾けてるんじゃない？
Isn't your heart beating faster, and my heart throbbing and thrilling?
いつじょいふる ふぉびふぅ で ぼぶぅ ばぶぅ
It's joyful fobifu de bobu babu
joy と joy と joy と pop な ベイビー
Joy and joy and joy and pop baby
joy と joy と joy と happy な ピーポー
Joy and joy and joy and happy people
joy と joy と joy と happy な セイエーーイ
Joy and joy and joy and happy say yeah!
じょいふる！！
Joyful!!
え、みんな一緒に歌ってくれてありがとうー！
"Everyone, thank you so much for singing with us!"
いやー、よかったねー！
"Man, that was great!"
会場がね、一体になったって感じでさ！ うん。
"It felt like the whole venue became one! Yeah."
よかったよかった！ テンション上がったわ、これ！
"That's great! My tension really went up!"
さ、さ、次は、いよいよ、カノンさんに歌っていただきます！
"Now, next, finally, Kanon-san will sing for us!"
君、大丈夫？
"Are you okay?"
え？ 何？
"Huh? What?"
なに？何の音？
"What? What's that sound?"
え？ うそっ…！
"Huh? No way...!"
あわ…あわ…って！
"Pan- Panic...!"
まさか！
"No way!"
コラプサー！
"A Collapser!"
取れないんだけど！ なにこれ！？
"I can't get it off! What is this!?"
ちょちょちょちょちょ！ なに？どういうこと？
"Wait, wait, wait! What? What do you mean?"
コラプサーだ！
"It's a Collapser!"
ですよねー！どう考えてもね、コラプサー！やっぱり…
"Right? No matter how you think about it, a Collapser! As expected..."
外してー！ やだ！痛い痛い痛い！
"Take it off! No! It hurts, hurts, hurts!"
わるっ！
"Bad!"
こわいこわいこわい！
"Scary, scary, scary!"
えーと、えー、こういうときは…
"U-Um, uh, in times like this..."
と、トリックオアトリート！
"T-Trick or treat!"
何にも噛む違うだろ！
"That's totally wrong!"
うわっ！
"Woah!"
え、うっ！うわぁっ！
"Ugh! Woah!"
ばかめ！天国が見なってるよ！
"Fools! You're seeing heaven!"
ふざけんな！ 出てろ、出てろ！
"Cut the crap! Get out, get out!"
楽しいの物がが出たな！
"Fun stuff came out!"
よいしょっ！
"Heave-ho!"
だが、コラプサーが出てくるってことは… 夢オチしてる人がいるんだ。たぶん。
"But for a Collapser to appear means... someone is having a dream ending. Probably."
みお先輩！
"Mio-senpai!"
みおちゃん！
"Mio-chan!"
ごめん…うち、うち、本当は、黒いのカボチャが怖くてだめなの…！
"Sorry... I-I actually am too scared of the black pumpkin...!"
え？
"Huh?"
ちっちゃいころ、パパがハロウィンで、あれかぶって帰ってきて…
"When I was little, my dad wore that for Halloween and came home..."
「ただいまー」うち、パパがカボチャに食べられちゃったんだって思っちゃって…
"Saying 'I'm home—' and I thought my dad was eaten by a pumpkin..."
それから、どうしても、ハロウィンのかぼちゃだけは無理なの…！
"Ever since then, I just can't handle Halloween pumpkins...!"
うわーーっ！
"Waaaaaah!"
なに？
"What?"
いやーっ！
"Nooo!"
チェンジ！
"Change!"
カリア・アーム！
"Callia Arm!"
見つめる、ロッタ！
"Glancing, Lotta!"
ロッタ！
"Notta!"
キャンディ・パラソル！
"Candy Parasol!"
頑張りな、マリン！
"Do your best, Marine!"
スノーフレーク・セイバー！
"Snowflake Saber!"
ぶっ切り丸！
"Bukkirimaru!"
ここは任せて、みお！
"Leave this to me, Mio!"
みんな…
"Everyone..."
この手を差し伸べ 掴んで 握る 天使の魔法 魔法少女 カナタ！
"Reach out this hand, grasp and hold it, the angel's magic! Magical Girl Kanata!"
みんなの願いを叶させる祈り ニコのほら 魔法少女 みこ！
"A prayer to grant everyone's wishes, Niko's behold, Magical Girl Miko!"
甘い幸せ おすそわけ 姫のほら 魔法少女 ルーナ！
"Sharing sweet happiness, the princess's behold, Magical Girl Luna!"
きらめくお宝から ロックオン！ 海賊のほら 魔法少女 マリン！
"Lock on from sparkling treasure! The pirate's behold, Magical Girl Marine!"
心踊らすトリックスタァ！ 狐のほら 魔法少女 ふぶき！
"Heart-dancing trickster! The fox's behold, Magical Girl Fubuki!"
積り積もる純白の愛
Overflowing with pure white love...
雪のホロウ魔法少女ラミィ
Snow's holy magic, Lamy!
ホロウッチ
Holowitch!
ガールキャスト
Girlcast!
パンプキン…だけじゃないぞ、まだまだよ！
This isn't just a pumpkin... it's still alive!
こい！
Come!
やめな！
Stop it!
ふっ！
Haah!
はあ…はあ…はあ…
Ah... hah... hah...
おいおいおいおい！
Oi, oi, oi, oi!
はあっ！
Haah!
ね、なんかこれまずくない？
Wait, isn't this getting worse?
どんどん強くなってる！
They're getting stronger!
みんながやつらを倒すより、不安と恐れが膨れ上がるほうが早いみたい！
Instead of beating them all, it looks like...
そんな！
What? Really?
ウチのせい…
Our fault...
ウチが…
It's our fault...
あんなもの怖いって思っちゃうせいで…
Just because we thought those things were scary...
そんなこと分かってるの。
You know that...
おかしいよね、あんなのがどうしようもなく怖いなんて。
It's funny, isn't it? How something like that can be so terrifying.
だから今日も我慢して頑張ろうって思ったのに…
That's why I tried to hold back today and do my best...
でも…でもやっぱり…
But still...
おかしくだなんてないよ。
There's nothing wrong with being silly.
カノンさん…
Con-san?
誰にだって苦手なものがある。怖いもの、嫌いなもの。人になんでそんなものがあるって言われても、どうしようもないことってやっぱりあるよ。
No matter who you are, everyone has things they're bad with, things they fear, and things they hate.
ねえ。
Right?
そうだな！
That's right!
何が苦手だとか、何が怖いこととかは関係なくて！
It doesn't matter what you're bad at or what you're afraid of!
大事なのは、みんながみおちゃんを信じたいって思ってるかどうかだから！
What's important is whether you want to believe in Mio-chan or not!
だから遠慮しないで！
So don't hold back!
頼ってほしいなら！
If you want to rely on us, then do it!
だってそうじゃん！私たちお互い様じゃん！
After all, we're all on each other's side!
誰かのつらさも誰かの苦手も、ほかの誰かがカバーする。
Someone's weakness or fear just means someone else will cover for them.
お互いそうやって助け合ってきたから！今だって！
We've always done that for each other, right?
こんなに頑張れる！
That's why we can try this hard!
ホロウッチ。コラプターは夢落ちした人の恐れと不安から生まれる。その心を深く沈ませて。
Holowitch. The collapse is born from the fear and anxiety of those who have fallen into despair.
夢落ちって…どうしてそれを？
Despair? Why would you say that?
でも…私は知ってる。
But... I know.
君たちなら、ホロウッチなら、つらい、苦しい、悲しい、きつい、そんな自分一人の力じゃ抜け出せない暗闇の中にいても、夢は光を届けてくれる。
If it's you guys, if it's Holowitch, even if you're in the painful, distressing, sad, and harsh darkness where you can't use your own strength alone... dreams can bring you light.
任せて、連れ出してあげる。
They'll pull you through.
たとえ悪夢の最中でも、まだ終わりじゃないから。
Even if the nightmare isn't over yet...
さあ、みんな。ホロウッチが戦ってくれる。では、私たちにできるのは？
Now, Holowitch will fight for you. So, what can we do?
そう！私たちの声で、思い出で、彼女たちを応援することだ！
That's right, with our voices and memories, to support them!
いざ、トリック・オア・トリート！
All right, trick or treat!
あれよと言う間に飲み込まれ
Swallowed up before you can even say "Here it comes!"
橙色のダイアルウェーブ 夜行 夜光
Orange-colored daylight wave, night-walking, night-glowing.
ハンドメイドから オーダーメイドまで 仕掛ける大流行 (hi!)
From handmade to custom-made, putting on a big trend (Hi!)
本物から偽物まで まとめて大集合 (hi!)
From the real to the fake, all gathered together (Hi!)
揃いも揃って不揃いな世界観に お揃いの幼さに腑抜けた恒例
Matching and mismatched worldviews, matching childishness, a cliché of custom.
催しの奴隷 夜通し踊れ 条例 処刑 フォーメーションで 褒美を獲れ
Dancing with urged slaves at night, formation with laws and execution, win praise.
ママ―レードが溶ける頃 (wo woi!)
When the masquerade melts away (Woo woi!)
キャパ以上に御道化る者 (wo woi!)
Those who become even more righteous than caps (Woo woi!)
チヤホヤされたりされたりが いいんですって？
Being fawned over and pampered is fine, right?
甘いだけじゃ物足りない give me some more (wahhh!)
Sweetness alone isn't enough, give me some more (Wahhh!)
浸れてく 溶けてゆく
Drowning, melting away...
夢のなか 夢のなか
...deep inside a dream, inside a dream.
問いかける 呼びかける
Questioning, calling out,
私の名を囁く
whispering my name.
あなたは誰 聴こえるか
Who are you? Can you hear me?
聴こえるわ 絶望の
I can hear it—the opening act
幕開きね 暗闇の帷が
of despair, as the dark curtain
上がる 恐いわ
rises. It's terrifying,
恐れさえ 狡いわ 甘美だろう
even the fear is cunning and sweet.
心が禁忌を犯す 鳴呼
The heart commits a taboo. Ah...
あなたこそが 私の天使
You are truly my angel.
重なる影ふたり 揺れる調べ
Two overlapping shadows, a swaying melody,
奈落の底に 堕ちてゆくまで
until we fall to the depths of the abyss.
この身捧げ 永遠を誓う
I offer this body and swear eternity.
罪さえ 隠すような 仮面
A mask that hides even our sins.
浸れてく 溶けてゆく
Drowning, melting away
胸のおく 胸のおく
deep within the chest, deep within.
ためらいに 手を伸ばす
Reaching out a hand in hesitation,
哀しげに喚く
crying out sorrowfully—
あなたの声 知りたいか
your voice. Do you want to know?
知りたいわ 喉元に
I want to know what wells up
湧き上がる 嘆きの正体を
in your throat—the true form of your sighs.
見せて 恐いの
Show me. It's frightening,
面影が 痛いの 魔魔をする
the lingering image hurts, playing the demon.
台本のない舞台で 鳴呼
On a stage without a script, ah...
思いのまま 奏でてみたい
I want to play just as I wish.
高鳴る旋律ひとつ 分かちつ秘密
A single throbbing melody, a shared secret,
見果てぬ場所へ 辿り着くまで
until we reach a place yet unseen.
愛おしさで 飾るドレス
A dress adorned with affection,
綻びも 贐ような 仮面
even flaws are masked as a farewell gift.
眩い シャンデリア
A dazzling chandelier,
泡の夢 白白の嬌声
a dream of bubbles, pure white cries.
運命のように 悪戯のように
Like fate, like mischief,
命火が燃え上がる
the flame of life burns brightly.
重なる影ふたり 揺れる調べ
Two overlapping shadows, a swaying melody,
奈落の底に 堕ちてゆくまで
until we fall to the depths of the abyss.
この身捧げ 永遠を誓う
I offer this body and swear eternity.
音楽の天使よ
O angel of music,
高鳴る旋律ひとつ 分かちつ秘密
a single throbbing melody, a shared secret,
見果てぬ場所へ 辿り着くまで
until we reach a place yet unseen.
愛おしさで 飾るドレス
A dress adorned with affection,
綻びも 贐ような 仮面
even flaws are masked as a farewell gift.
浸れてく 溶けてゆく
Drowning, melting away...
本性露わに暴れよ
Reveal your true nature and run wild!
その姿も正装になる
Even that appearance becomes formal attire.
狂騒曲のTurnable
The turnable of this masquerade rhapsody,
愛々しい溜まり We got a party night!
We got a party night!
眠れやしない Oh night Oh night
We can't sleep all through the night!
鳴りやまない Oh night Oh night
It's unending all through the night!
古代の空あそび
Playing in the skies of ancient times,
あなたはまるで魂
you are just like a soul.
遺跡機械ジャンボリー
An ancient ruins jamboree,
目覚めさせてHalloween!
wake it up, Halloween!
骨抜きダンスを
A bone-shaking dance,
スクエアクロモ 飛び跳ね回る
square the clock and leap around!
Holo!
好きよのタンテボ クルクルクル
Our favorite turntables spinning round and round!
愛おしい溜まり We got a party night!
We got a party night!
カボチャの力が乱れてる…
The pumpkin's power is going haywire...
恐れと不安が溶けていくんだ。
Our fear and anxiety are melting away.
歌の力…？
The power of song...?
みんなの、声の力で…！
With the power of everyone's voices...!
さあ、行って！ホロウィッチ、心を欺くトリックに、飛びきりのトリートを！
Now go! Give those who deceive hearts a dazzling treat!
フブちゃんのトリックスター！
Fubuki's Trickster!
みんな声援ありがとう！もうすぐだよ、
Thank you all for the cheers! It's almost time,
楽しんじゃうよ！
let's have fun!
トリック！イッテン！
Trick! Hit 'em!
ラミィちゃんがんばれ～！ / ホロウィッチがんばれ！
Lamy-chan, do your best! We're cheering for you!
信じるからね みんなの愛が力をくれる！
Believe in it! Everyone's love gives us strength!
トリック！イッテン！
Trick! Hit 'em!
ラミィちゃんナイス！それじゃあ決めちゃおよ！
Lamy-chan, nice! Then let's decide it!
ユニディアラミネーション！
Uni-dia Laminiation!
スラッシュアンドコンクエスト！
Slash and Conquest!
ユニディアラミネーション！
Unidia Lamination!
スラッシュアンドコンクエスト！
Slash and Conquest!
眠れ眠れ先輩
Sleep, sleep, Senpai!
３秒あなた!
Three seconds for you!
せーの、レリコットスフィア！
Ready, go! Relicott Sphere!
みんなミコのえりーとなとこ そんなに似合わないんだ
Everyone says Miko's elite side doesn't suit her at all!
しょうがないね！
Oh well, can't help it!
みんなと一緒に！
Everyone, together!
タイムアウトだリュマステイバー！プリンセスステイバー！
Time's out! Lumasteyver! Princess-steyver!
がんばれ！かなた！
Do your best, Kanata!
船長、私たちがいつもそばにいるからね！
Captain, we'll always be by your side!
必殺！リングイネ！オーバースプラッシュガール！
Special Move! Linguine! Over Splash Girl!
あいつらでラストだ！
They're the last ones!
チームだよ、みんな！
We're a team, everyone!
チェンジ！ホロウィッチステッキ！
Change! HoloWitch Stick!
フルキャスト！
Full Cast!
みお先輩、もう大丈夫そう？
Mio-senpai, are you alright now?
あ、うん…その見ないようにすれば、なんとか…
Ah, yeah... If I just try not to look, somehow...
分かるよ。白神も高いとこ行くと足震えないからね。
I get it. Shirakami's knees shake too when she goes somewhere high.
あくたん、もう虫はなるべく見ないようにしてるなら。
Akutan, if you're trying not to look at bugs as much as possible now.
ありがとう、みんな。
Thank you, everyone.
みんなが助けてくれたみたいに、うちもみんなが辛いとき、苦しいときがあったら…
Just like everyone helped me out, if any of you are going through a painful or tough time...
絶対、絶対力になるから！
I will definitely, definitely be your strength!
そで、これでめでたしめでたし。
Well, all's well that ends well.
でもいいんだけどさ、
That's fine and all, but...
みんな！ホロウイッチの活躍、もっと見たいんじゃない？
Everyone! Don't you want to see Holowitch's adventures even more?
だそうだけど。
That's what they say, but...
え？こっち？こっち撮るの？
Eh? This way? You're filming this way?
え、あ、や、やります！
Eh, ah, y-yes, I can do it!
よーし、やるよ、みんな！
Alright, let's do this, everyone!
♪
[Music]
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to fear; we are no longer alone.
大切な何かが 壊れたあの夜に
On the night when something precious broke,
僕は星を探して 一人で歩いていた
I searched for the stars and walked alone.
ペルセウス座流星群 君も見てただろうか
I wonder if you saw the Perseid meteor shower too.
僕は元気にやってるよ 君は今「どこ」にいるの？
I'm doing well. Where are you right now?
「方法」という悪魔にとり憑かれないで
Don't get possessed by a devil called "method,"
「目的」という大事なものを思い出して
and remember what's truly important: your "goal."
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to fear; we are no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖くても大丈夫 僕らはもう一人じゃない
Even if we're scared, it's alright; we are no longer alone.
大切な何かが 壊れたあの夜に
On the night when something precious broke,
僕は君を探して 一人で歩いていた
I searched for you and walked alone.
あの日から僕らは 一人で海を目指す
Ever since that day, we walk toward the sea alone.
「約束のあの場所で 必ずまた逢おう。」と
"We will surely meet again at that promised place."
「世間」という悪魔に 惑わされないで
Don't be misled by a devil called "society,"
自分だけが決めた「答え」を思い出して
and remember the "answer" you alone decided on.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to fear; we are no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖くても大丈夫 僕らはもう一人じゃない
Even if we're scared, it's alright; we are no longer alone.
“煌めき”のような 人生の中で
In a life that sparkles like starlight,
君に出逢えて 僕は本当に良かった
I am so glad I got to meet you.
街を抜け海に出たら 次はどこを目指そうか
When we leave the town and reach the sea, where should we head next?
僕らはまた出かけよう 愛しいこの地球を
Let's set out once more across this lovely Earth.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to fear; we are no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖くても大丈夫 僕らはもう一人じゃない
Even if we're scared, it's alright; we are no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to fear; we are no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖くても大丈夫 僕らはもう一人じゃない
Even if we're scared, it's alright; we are no longer alone.
空は青く澄み渡り 海を目指して歩く
The sky is clear and blue as I walk toward the sea.
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to fear; we are no longer alone.
空は青 くすみはさり 海を目指して歩く
The sky is blue, the haze clears, walking toward the sea
怖いものなんてない 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to fear, we are no longer alone anymore
空は青 くすみはさり 海を目指して歩く
The sky is blue, the haze clears, walking toward the sea
怖くても大丈夫 僕らはもう一人じゃない
There's nothing to fear, we are no longer alone anymore
みんな、今日はありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for today!
最高に楽しいハロウィンだったよね、みんな！
It was the best Halloween ever, everyone!
ちょっとアクシデントもあったけどさ、そういうのも含めていい思い出になったんじゃない？
We had a few accidents too, but it's all part of the good memories!
よかったー！
I'm so glad!
いいお宝...
Good treasure...
思い出...
Memories...
さて、そろそろお時間となってまいりましたが
Well, it's almost time...
アンコール！アンコール！アンコール！
Encore! Encore! Encore!
それじゃアンコールにお答えして、この曲歌っちゃうなら！
Well then, in response to the encore, let's sing this song!
始まりの魔法-charm-！
The starting magic -charm-!
はじまりの魔法-charm-
[Title: Hajimari no Mahou -charm-]
きみに魔法をかけるよ
I will cast a spell on you
we cast a spell on your dream!!
はじまりを告げる衝動が響く
The impulse that signals the start rings out
気づいた時がいつだってスタートラインなんだ
Whenever you notice it, that's always your starting line
何者でもなかった日々を変えたのは
What changed those days when I was nothing
見つけたばかりのちっぽけな輝きの原石
Was the small, newly discovered rough stone of brilliance
「どうして私だけうまくいかないんだろう」
"Why is it that only I can't do things well?"
自分以外の全てが眩しくみえるけど
Everything other than myself looks dazzling, but
ねぇきみに見つけてほしくて
Hey, I wanted you to find me
なりたい私になる今こそ
Now is the time to become the me I want to be
そうだ！叶えたい掴みたい夢があるから
That's right! Because I have a dream I want to fulfill
塞ぎこんだ日のことも連れて踏み出すんだ
I'll take the days I spent closed off with me and step forward
信じる力が奇跡を起こすように
Just like the power of believing creates miracles
きみに魔法をかけるよ
I will cast a spell on you
we cast a spell on your dream!!
叶った望みと叶わない願い
Fulfilling wishes and unfulfilled desires
それぞれが等しく流れてく世界で
In this world where each flows equally
何を求めて歩き続けるんだろう
What am I seeking and continuing to walk for?
そんなことばかり迷うけれど
I'm lost with just those kinds of things, but
きみがくれたこの空が
This sky you gave me
消えない翼をくれたね
Gave me wings that won't disappear, didn't it?
そうだ！照らしたいとどけたい人がいるから
That's right! Because there are people I want to illuminate
誰ひとり置いてけたりしないとそう決めたんだ
I decided that I wouldn't leave anyone behind
愛したい応えたい自分自身feeling
The feel of myself wanting to love, wanting to respond
正解なんて越えていこう
Let's go beyond "correct answers"
未体験のstage!!
An unexperienced stage!!
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine
どんな姿でもいい
Any form is fine
追いかけたいんだあのきらめきを
I want to chase after that sparkle
「希望」
"Hope"
「苦悩」
"Anguish"
抱きしめて持っていこう
Let's hold them and take them with us
ほら繋げたい広げたい可能性(みち)があるから
Look, because there is a path I want to connect and expand
ここからはじまる物語を一緒に行こう
Let's go together on the story that starts from here
信じる力が奇跡を起こすように
Just like the power of believing creates miracles
この手をにぎってひとりじゃないから
Take this hand, because you're not alone
きみに魔法をかけるよ
I will cast a spell on you
we cast a spell on your dream!!
消えない翼をくれたね
Gave me wings that won't disappear, didn't it?
照らしたい届けたい人がいるから
Because there are people I want to illuminate, I want to reach
ひとり置いてったりしない
I won't leave anyone behind
愛したい応えたい自分自身の秘め事
The secret of myself wanting to love, wanting to respond
世界なんてこれぜんぶ見たいけんのせい
A world like this is all thanks to unexperienced sights
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine
どんな姿でもいい
Any form is fine
追いかけたいんだあのきらめきを
I want to chase after that sparkle
きみに魔法をかけるよ
I will cast a spell on you
we cast a spell on your dream!!
どんな場所でもいいよ
Any place is fine
どんな姿でもいい
Any form is fine
追いかけたいんだあのきらめきを
I want to chase after that sparkle
希望を抱きしめてもっていこう
Let's hold hope and take it with us
ほら繋げたい広げたい道があるから
Look, because there is a path I want to connect and expand
ここから始まる物語を一緒にいこう
Let's go together on the story that starts from here
信じる力が奇跡を起こすように
Just like the power of believing creates miracles
この手をにぎってひとりじゃないから
Take this hand, because you're not alone
きみに魔法をかけるよ
I will cast a spell on you
we cast a spell on your dream!!
信じる力が奇跡を起こすように
Just like the power of believing creates miracles
この手をにぎってひとりじゃないから
Take this hand, because you're not alone
きみに魔法をかけるよ
I will cast a spell on you
We cast a spell on you...
we cast a spell on your dream ！！
We cast a spell on your dream!!
はじまりを告げる 衝動が響く
An impulse announcing the beginning echoes.
気づいた時が いつだってスタートラインなんだ
Whenever you realize it, that's always your starting line.
最高なステージだったよ、ホロウィッチ！
That was the best stage ever, HoloWitch!
本当、本当！
Really, really!
みんな、お疲れ様！
Good work, everyone!
カノンさん、あの……
Kanon-san, um...
今日は、本当にありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for today.
それで、あなたはどして、夢落ちとか僕たちのことを……
So, why do you know about dream-drops and about us...?
私、前に夢落ちして、きみたちに助けられたことがあるんだ。
I once suffered a dream-drop and was saved by you guys.
ええっ！？
Eh?!
だから、あの時の自分と同じように、夢落ちして苦しんでいる誰かを見ると、ほっとけなくて。
So when I see someone suffering from a dream-drop just like I did, I can't just leave them be.
あと、実は……今日このステージに出ることにしたのも、きみたちがでるって聞いたからなんだ。もう一度会えたらって思って。
And actually... the reason I decided to be on this stage today was because I heard you guys were performing. I hoped we could meet again.
だから今日は、えっと……すごく嬉しかった！これからもがんばってね、ホロウィッチ！
So today, um... I was so happy! Do your best from now on too, HoloWitch!
それじゃ……また！ぜひまた！
Well then... see you! Please let's meet again!
あの人自身が夢落ちしてホロウィッチに助けられていたから……
Because that person himself had suffered a dream-drop and been saved by HoloWitch...
知っていたんだ。夢落ちしたときのつらさも、そんなとき誰かが手を差し伸べてくれることの嬉しさも。
He knew. The pain of suffering a dream-drop, and the joy of someone reaching out a hand in times like that.
そっか。ミコたちが少しでも誰かの力になれたら、
I see. If Miko and the others can be of help to someone, even just a little—
その誰かがまた別の誰かの力になってくれるんだね。
that someone will become the strength of someone else.
そうだね。しかもさ、そんだけじゃなくて、後ろの力になってくれたりもするわけじゃん。
That's right. And besides, they even become a strength standing behind us.
あの人や今日応援してくれたみんなみたいに。それって……
Like that person and everyone who cheered for us today. That is...
それってすっごくトリート！
That's a super treat!
きらきら星空みたいに 心が輝いてよ
Sparkle like a starry sky, let your heart shine on!
夢の結晶 見失っちゃうことも あるけど
Sometimes we lose sight of the crystallization of our dreams, but—
あふれ出した 光が僕を呼ぶんだよ
The overflowing light is calling out to me!
絶対大丈夫 ただまっすぐでいること まらくちゃない日もあるよね
It'll definitely be alright. Just staying straight—though some days aren't easy, right?
あきらめも苦しみも重なっていく ここらとき、あなたと
Let's stack up our resignation and suffering too, with you...
夢を歌おう魔法に乗せて 何度も立ち上がるきみと一緒に進んでく
Let's sing our dreams, carried by magic, advancing forward together with you!
夢は夢は終わらない 未来をとり戻すんだ
Dreams will never end. We will take back our future!
なんのって笑って もう一歩一歩歩き始めよう
Laughing no matter what, let's take another step forward once more!
ホロウィッチおやさい 夢の先へ
HoloWitch, onwards to the future of our dreams!
ワクワクするような 日々と夢の結晶 思い出して魔法を唱えてみたら
Days that make you excited and the crystallization of your dreams—if you remember them and chant a magic spell...
ドキドキするような きみの物語 何度でも……
Your heart-pounding story, over and over again...
光り…光りだすんだよ
Light... it starts to shine!
頑張ってたってても…
No matter how hard I try...
もううまくいかない日の方が多く感じちゃったりするよね
It feels like there are more days that don't go my way.
かなえよう、不安も
Let's grant our wishes, even the anxieties,
悲しみも語れないぜ
and the sorrows we can't speak of.
一人じゃない
We are not alone.
希望の種を
The seeds of hope...
汗に泣いたら一番に輝く綺麗な花が咲くよ
If we cry through our sweat, the brightest, most beautiful flower will bloom.
夢を歌おうよ
Let's sing of our dreams,
魔法に乗っけて何度も立ち上がる君と一緒に進んでく
riding on magic, getting back up again and again, moving forward together with you!
夢は夢は涙を流さない
Dreams, dreams don't shed tears,
未来をどこまでも行こう
Let's go to the future no matter where!
何度だって笑ってもう一回行こう
Laugh no matter what, and let's go once more!
歩き始めようホロウィッチを飛ばそう夢の先へ
Let's start walking, making HoloWitch soar toward the edge of our dreams!